<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Pebble Connect</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome to Pebble Connect with httpebble support, this app allows your Pebble smart watch to communicate with 
        the Internet, access your location, store data and receive notifications. This app does not need to be open or running to be used
        by your Pebble. 	</string>
	<string name="getStarted">To get started, check out some <a href="https://ofkorth.net/pebble/watchfaces">httpebble watch faces</a>.
	</string>
	<string name="notifications">If you would like to get notifications or use IFTTT with your Pebble, 
	    visit the <a href="http://lukekorth.com/blog/restful-pebble/">Cloud Access</a> section</string>
    <string name="info">This app uses the <a href="http://kathar.in/httpebble/">httpebble protocol</a>. Further information and support can be found
        in the <a href="http://forums.getpebble.com/">Pebble forums</a>. 	</string>
    <string name="source">The source code can be found on 		<a href="https://github.com/lkorth/httpebble-android">GitHub</a>.
	</string>
	
    <string name="explanation">Cloud Access allows your Pebble to receive notifications and data from the Internet. Your Pebble can 
        be used as a channel on <a href="https://ifttt.com/">If This Then That</a> or you can use the API to integrate with just about
        anything else. For more information please see the <a href="http://lukekorth.com/blog/restful-pebble/">documentation</a>.</string>
        
    <string name="auth">These are your user id and user tokens. They are used to send data to your Pebble, anyone with your id and
        token can send data to your Pebble, so keep them safe. Please choose something unique for your user id such as your email.
        Changing your token at anytime will invalidate you previous token and not allow it to send data to your Pebble.</string>

</resources>